what happen inside that's cool the search for a motive in a knife attack on fellow students in tonight emotional reunion prepare a best friend who helped save each other hitting home R series on the heroin epidemic in the sky
发生什么事了里面很酷的搜索在同学今晚情绪团聚持刀行凶动机准备谁拯救了对方打回家R系列的海洛因疫情在天空中最好的朋友
brave mom who song on the very day shift save her own son from an overdose
勇敢的妈妈谁的歌就很有白班除她自己的儿子从过量
another big surprise in late night television Nightly News begins now
在深夜的电视晚间新闻的另一大惊喜现在开始
this is NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
这是NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
grieving police
警方悲伤
caters are very anxious to learn what the motive was behind the knife attack on fellow students in a high school in a Pittsburgh suburbs
迎合非常渴望了解什么样的动机是对同学们的持刀行凶的一所高中在匹兹堡郊区的背后
the young man being held is 16 is being charged as an adult it was a violent frenzy 2 of his victims are still critical yet another school
这个年轻人正在举行的是16充电时，作为一个成年人，这是他的受害者的暴力狂潮2仍然至关重要又一所学校
America is drawing together now after an awful tragedy we begin their again tonight Peter Alexander at Franklin Regional High School
美国正在一起绘制后，现在一个可怕的悲剧，我们开始他们今晚再次彼得·亚历山大·富兰克林地方高中
brian Griffin to you police say they are still interviewing witnesses end tonight source is close to the investigation tell NBC News at this time there is no evidence to suggest that the suspect at any specific target did the victims were like we selected at random
布赖恩·格里芬给您警方说，他们仍在与证人会面结束今晚来源是接近调查告诉NBC新闻在这个时候，没有证据表明，犯罪嫌疑人在任何特定的目标并受害者是像我们随机选择
this evening a window into those horrifying moments is first responder Florida fishes attack Franklin Regional High School
今天晚上一个窗口，进入那些可怕的时刻是第一个响应佛罗里达州鱼类攻击富兰克林地方高中
call reporting 111 life
打电话汇报生活111
the severity of the situation quickly became clear
形势的严重性很快就清楚
the suspect 16 year old Alex hribal remains behind bars charged as an adult with attempted homicide an aggravated assault rifles attorney at his parents visiting briefly today
犯罪嫌疑人16岁的亚历克斯hribal仍然落后充电作为一个成年人与杀人未遂的严重攻击步枪的律师在他的父母今天来访的简要酒吧
visa to Paris with very much in love with her two sons ages to see this coming
签证到巴黎与非常爱她的两个儿子的年龄，看看这个未来
investigators are still trying to figure out what sparked the rampage
研究者们仍在试图弄清楚什么引发了横冲直撞
is UConn a Magin a crime scene was quite Bloody I was clothing and personal belongings currently conducting an investigation deducting interviews of the victims and witnesses
康涅狄格大学是一个Magin犯罪现场相当血腥的我的衣服和个人物品目前正进行调查扣除受害者和证人的采访
under investigation the possibility of an angry phone call between the suspect at another student the night before the attack 521 students at a security guard most severely wounded 70 junior Jared Boger a member of the local ski patrol who underwent a second surgery overnight
接受调查的犯罪嫌疑人在另一名学生的攻击521的学生在保安的前一天晚上最严重的伤员70初中贾里德表征Boger谁接受了第二次手术过夜当地的滑雪巡逻队的成员愤怒的电话呼叫的可能性
Houston critical condition is still will require a funeral processions
休斯顿临界条件仍需要一个葬礼游行
software Chapel Sally's recovering at home right around here at first I didn't even realize he been stopped before a teacher and student classroom thinking like him how long we going to be Hamlet a lot of blood really fast
在家软件教堂Sally的恢复权利在这里一开始我什至没有意识到他被老师和学生的课堂像他这样想着之前停止多久，我们将是哈姆雷特很多血真快
houses kind of scandal bleed to death Amanda Leonard son bread was stabbed in the back
样的丑闻流血过多死亡阿曼达伦纳德儿子面包房子被刺伤背部
when my daughter called me at work yesterday freaking out and told me that my son was on the list of victims
当我的女儿在工作昨天打电话给我吓坏了，告诉我，我的儿子遇难者名单上
Texas best friend to stay with him until paramedics arrive
和他呆在一起，直到救护人员抵达德州最好的朋友
is Kitchen
是厨房
we were invited to the hospital today went crazy
我们被邀请去医院走到今天疯狂
he saved your life
他救过你的命
he did his microphone
他做了他的麦克风
where is she said my life in Italian Kissimmee from bleeding out
哪里是她说我在意大利的奥兰多生活渗出
friendship now strangers might rattle
友谊现在陌生人可能嘎嘎
forgot your pass always you know that
忘记您的通行证总是你知道，
good news this afternoon Brian Brentwood home for the hospital he says his main goal is to get back on his feet so he can dance at prom
好消息，今天下午布莱恩布伦特伍德的家，他说，他的主要目标是要取回他的脚，所以他可以在跳舞的舞会医院
what a turn of events Murrysville Pennsylvania Peter Alexander starting a soft Peter thanks now that we go to the Pacific Northwest the death toll has been slowly rising
事件MURRYSVILLE宾夕法尼亚州彼得·亚历山大开始软彼得感谢一个什么样的现在轮到我们去西北太平洋的死亡人数已经上升缓慢
in the almost 3 weeks now since the mudslide level data tire town in Washington State
在近3个星期了，因为泥石流级数据的轮胎镇在华盛顿州
3600 people are now confirmed dead and search ur still looking for 1000 and tonight for the first time we're hearing from a young mother a survivor who was pulled from the debris along with her young baby and we get her story tonight from NBC's Miguel Almaguer
3600人现在确认死亡和搜索乌尔仍在寻找1000和今晚是第一次，我们正在从一个年轻的母亲谁是从与她年轻的婴儿残骸拉到一个幸存者听到，我们从NBC的米格尔Almaguer让她今晚的故事
can I find my neighbors house coming out man turns
我能找到我的邻居的房子走出来的男人轮流
Pinterest screamed out God favors
Pinterest的尖叫上帝的恩惠
tremendous Koreans time will heal her damaged eye socket broken legs in arm with a painful memories will always haunt her
巨大的韩国人时间会抚平她损坏的眼圈断脚时手臂与一个痛苦的回忆将永远困扰着她
what that are front door
什么是前门
is it was like a movie
是它像一部电影
houses were explored in the next thing I remember is our neighbors chimney coming into her front doors
房子进行了探讨，在未来的事情，我记得是我们的邻居烟囱进入她的前门
unturned Duke
千方百计公爵
Duke for 6 month old baby boy was in her arms when the wave of Mudd smash their home
杜克6个月大的男婴被抱在怀里的时候穆德的波粉碎他们的家
what was not letting that baby go
什么是不让宝宝去
what was not let me go
什么也不让我走
is a little blue
是一个小蓝
what was the name
叫什么名字
Aarons
阿伦斯
163 with me bird
163我鸟
in this bass Dupree field remarkably Amanda's cry for help
在这个低音杜普里领域显着阿曼达的求救声
she was cut from the rubble Duke carried out clinging to life by a group of strangers amanda is not yet met
她从废墟中被切公爵进行了一群陌生人阿曼达执着于生活尚未满足
I will pay it forward for the rest of my life
我将支付它前进为我的余生
amother who lost so much grateful for what she still has Miguel Almaguer NBC News
amother谁失去了这么多感谢她仍然有米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻
search teams of Australia say there is more encouraging progress tonight in the effort to find that Malaysia Airlines flight 370
澳大利亚的搜索队说有更多令人鼓舞的进展，今晚在努力寻找，马来西亚航空公司飞行370
trillion search plane has picked up new pings now commanders believe they are likely from those black boxes up to 3 miles beneath the ocean surface
万亿搜索飞机已经拿起新的ping现在指挥官相信，他们很可能从这些黑盒子长达3英里的海洋表面之下
date night from NBC's Tom Costello
约会之夜从NBC的汤姆·科斯特洛
on board the Australian ship ocean shield what may be proved the flight 370
船上的澳大利亚海洋船舶盾什么可以证明飞行370
coming from the plane's black box is the newest pans work picked up from a listening device hanging from a floating buoy 1000 feet below the ocean surface
从飞机的黑盒子来，是最新的平底锅工作拾起从一个监听装置悬挂在1000英尺以下的海面漂浮浮标
the data was and transmitted to an Air Force planes overhead now the race to capture as possible before the batteries die
该数据是并传输到空军飞机在头顶上现在比赛进行到捕捉尽可能之前，电池死
just trying to get all those little dots to line up the kind of say yeah this is the area that we want to search searching is still going to take him weeks do that survey
只是试图让所有那些小点来排队的那种说是啊，这就是我们想要搜索搜索领域的仍是要带他周做调查
search things must use the data from unknown pain location to Holden on the record below butt with just a few sets of being underwater search zone is 500 square miles roughly the size of Phoenix it would take weeks for men silver ring using sonar to stand at area of the ocean floor
搜索的东西必须使用不明疼痛部位的数据霍顿在屁股下面的记录，只需几台是水下搜索区域是500平方英里的凤凰差不多大小，将使用声纳站在区域需要数周的男性银戒指洋底
the more pings now the smaller the search zone
现在更多的ping的搜索区域较小
of course part in the black boxes will be critical to solving a mystery why does plane lost contact with controllers Appaloosa 4 of course taking the lives of 239 people Bryant
当然，在黑箱的一部分将是至关重要的解决一个谜为什么飞机失去了与控制器当然阿帕4服用239人科比的生活接触
Tom Costello in RDC newsroom tonight um thanks today President Obama pay tribute to the legacy of one of his predecessors saying he himself has lived out the promise of the Civil Rights Act passed by Lyndon Johnson half a century ago
汤姆·科斯特洛在RDC编辑部今晚嗯感谢今天奥巴马总统赞扬他的前任之一，他说，他自己已经住了民权法案的通过林登·约翰逊在半个世纪前通过的承诺的遗产
are cheap White House correspondent Chuck Todd was there at the LBJ Presidential Library and texts
便宜白宫记者查托德在那里的林登·约翰逊总统图书馆和文本
3 days after becoming President Lyndon Baines Johnson made a promise about civil rights phone call to Martin Luther King
成为总统后第3天林登·贝恩斯·约翰逊做出了承诺，对公民权利的电话给马丁·路德·金
bike one of the great products of a better grade
自行车一个更好的成绩的伟大的产品
grocery store tomorrow and you can count on Madison Ave do my best to get a man to do likewise
杂货店明天，你可以在麦迪逊大道指望尽我所能，让男人也这样做
and a half century later a celebration of a promise kept
半世纪后庆祝的承诺保持
what I meant to be on the outside what's his place
我的意思是在外面有什么自己的位置
in the making their lives better was what the hell the presidency was born
在使他们的生活更好的是什么地狱总统诞生
presidential legacy Vietnam LBJ's Family odds of 50th anniversary of the Civil Rights Act picture daughter Lynda Bird Johnson Robb
的民权法案画面的女儿琳达伯德·约翰逊罗博50周年总统的遗产越南林登·约翰逊的家庭赔率
nothing he would be proud of what we've done and he would also say we have for dinner go and we all need to keep peanut the eye on the prize
没有什么，他会是我们做了什么，他也说我们有吃饭去，我们都需要保持花生眼睛对奖骄傲
3 day celebration of the LBJ Library brought together presidents past and present in a pantheon of civil rights era clothing Congressman John Lewis still bears the scars of that struggle
3天庆祝林登·约翰逊图书馆带来了总统过去和现在的民权时代服装众议员的万神殿一起约翰·刘易斯仍承担这一斗争的伤痕
President Obama would not be president if the new Johnson and not pass the Civil Rights Act of 1964 and the Voting Rights Act of 6 & 5 secrets the climate
奥巴马总统不会​​成为总统，如果新的约翰逊和没有通过1964年的民权法案和6＆5机密气候的投票权法案
hand made it possible
手成为可能
Samantha color to be elected president
萨曼莎颜色当选总统
and its legacy that LBJ's family and friends hope someday Chuck Todd NBC News Austin Texas
其遗产，林登·约翰逊的家人和朋友希望有一天查托德NBC新闻得克萨斯州奥斯汀
and there is breaking political news tonight out of Washington NBC News has confirmed Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius is resigning after 5 years on the job
且有政治新闻，今晚出的华盛顿NBC新闻已经确认卫生和人类服务部部长凯瑟琳西贝柳斯是5年的工作后辞职
and following the Rocky roll out of President Obama's healthcare law she was the president appoint person to implement a law she come under fire numeral
和落基摇出奥巴马总统的医疗保健法律下，她是总统任命的人实施法律，她受到火灾数字
times from Republicans especially their what calls her job back when the website debuted as a giant debacle she was allowed to stay on through the deadline
从共和党时代尤其是他们的什么叫她的工作回当网站开张了作为一个巨大的崩溃，她被允许留在通过最后期限
a painful day on Wall Street today image concerns about another possible tech bubble on the rise the Nasdaq sides biggest one day fall in more than 2
约上另一种可能的技术泡沫上升纳斯达克双方最大单日跌幅超过2今天华尔街图像的担忧痛苦的一天
Sears of more than 3 Dow and S&P fell sharply as well go ahead for us this evening the steering impact of the current her when epidemic in America
超过3道指和标普西尔斯大幅下跌，以及继续为我们今天晚上当前她的转向影响，当疫情在美国
family including one of our viewers who came before the other night after seeing a report opening up about her fight to save her son and later a man who came to represent Boston strong the amazing changes in his life now one year later
家族，包括我们的其中一个浏览者看到的报告开拓了她的战斗拯救她的儿子，后来一个人谁便成了波士顿强在他的生活中的惊人变化，现在一年过去了后，其他前一天晚上来了谁
all this week here we been reporting on the heroin epidemic in parts of this country in at the heart of all of this are the families
所有这星期在这里，我们一直在报道的海洛因疫情在这个国家的在这一切的心脏部分是家庭
what are battling to help their love ones overcome their addictions and overcome overdoses we have heard from a lot of family including one mother outside Boston to reach out what national correspondent in the studio tonight
什么是作战，以帮助他们的亲人克服他们的瘾，克服我们已经从很多家庭包括一位母亲波士顿郊外的听说过量伸手在工作室什么国家的记者今晚
Brian so many people so many messages start my son my brother my daughter in late Monday 1 about a young man who Dover does Enrique was revived with the drug called narcan
布赖恩这么多人这么多的消息开始我的儿子我的兄弟我在周一晚1个女儿一个年轻人谁多佛也恩里克复兴与药物称为narcan
in a suburb of Boston his mom wrote song was almost taken and I see you tonight after 3 doses narcan thank God paramedics had it all we found her
在波士顿的郊区，他的妈妈写的歌几乎采取了，我看你今晚之后3个剂量narcan感谢上帝，医护人员拥有了一切，我们发现她
family adventure Helen back this week dani is the second oldest 6 kids last week overdose on heroin and this Monday morning he saw himself up for outpatient rehab but then wanted one last high
家庭冒险海伦回到本周丹妮是第二个最古老的6个孩子的海洛因，这周一早晨上周过量，他看到了自己的门诊康复治疗，但当时就想最后一个高
mom Debbie says most of the family was home when Danny's older brother found him from Dover in his room
妈妈黛比说，大多数家庭是家庭，当丹尼的哥哥发现他从多佛在他的房间
live in a text saying yes
生活在一个文本说是
her daughter Samantha was trying to shield her 9 year old sister from seeing her big brother like this
她的女儿萨曼莎试图从看到这样的她的大哥哥保护她9岁的妹妹
MSM and dad holding her and that's when she looked at me and says he gonna live until birth and crying
男男性接触者和爸爸抱着她，当她看着我那，说他要去现场，直到出生和哭泣
Danny's diseases affecting everyone in this family has his father David you don't sleep
影响大家在这个家庭丹尼的疾病有他父亲大卫你不睡觉
my teenager is in a stress out about it
我十几岁是一个压力了吧
it's hard to try to explain to a 9 year old what drug abuse is
很难试图解释一个9岁的什么药滥用
in the corner of her sons hospital room Debbie was calling residential rehab facilities it's a struggle many families face there's no guidebook for rehab centers in insurance does an awesome cover Link residential
在她儿子的医院房间的角落黛比在呼唤住宅康复设施，这是一个斗争，许多家庭面临没有指南，供保险康复中心做的真棒盖住宅链接
you have to be on the phone with a full time job I have 6 kids
你必须要在手机上用一份全职工作，我有6个孩子
managing an addiction is a full time job
管理一个成瘾是一个全职工作
she cant wait for a bed to open in a state run facility O'Sheas found a spot at a private rehab in Tennessee family members are loan in the $20
她不能等待床位的状态运行设施O'Sheas发现一个斑点在一个私人康复在田纳西州的家庭成员都在20元的贷款，以打开
praying that works really work
祈祷的作品真的工作
looking through photos yesterday and Debbie came across a birthday card any Roden
通过照片看昨天和黛比遇到了一个生日卡上的任何罗登
e-value time with me and everyone else in the family telling his mom how much she means to him I'm running a long time I need to hear that stay from him
e值的时间与我和其他人在家庭中告诉他的妈妈，她多少对他意味着我跑很长一段时间，我需要听到他的逗留
and I know he's going to say it again
我知道他会再说一遍
tonight dani is on his way to Tennessee to start treatment
今晚丹妮是在他的途中到田纳西州开始治疗
I'm not ashamed of my son I'm proud of my son and I love him with every fiber of my being in there is nothing
我不以为耻我的儿子我为我的儿子感到自豪，我爱他，我在那里幸福的每一根纤维是什么
I won't do to make sure that I give him every shot at recovery
我不会做，以确保我给他每一次出手处于复苏
the drug that saved Andrea on Monday is narcan update on star story from last week about that the governor of Maine have told us he opposed allowing parents to have narcan but this week changed course he now supports making it available immediately family members under certain conditions
救了安德烈周一药物是从上上周明星的故事有关缅因州州长告诉我们，他反对让家长有narcan但本周改变了路线，他现在支持使得它在一定条件下可立即家属narcan更新
running a lot of eyes with your work your case no one else is part of the series kpax we are back in a moment but the forecast just released that has millions paying close attention
你的工作你的情况没有别人跑了很多目光的是该系列KPAX我们又回到了片刻，但预测刚发布了一个拥有数百万密切关注的一部分
we learn today the third and final component of a complete change in late night is now in place today Stephen Colbert was named to succeed David Letterman steps of side sometime next year Colbert as part of the comedy graduating class
我们今天学习的深夜进行彻底的改变的第三个和最后一个组成部分是现在的地方今天斯蒂芬Colbert被命名为明年的某个时候科尔伯特接替大卫·莱特曼的步骤侧作为喜剧毕业班的一部分
behind a fan along with Jimmy Kimmel on a VCR on Jimmy Fallon Evelyn mount a something real close to a generational shift after your late local news Colbert send Ave He will host as himself meaning he will drop the character the persona he uses to host The Colbert Report
后面还有吉米金梅尔上吉米Fallon伊夫林录像机风扇安装一个东西真正的接近一个世代交替后，您下旬本地新闻科尔伯特发送大道，他将主持他自己的意思，他会掉落的字符，他使用主办科尔伯特的角色报告
is 49 years old is signed a five-year deal worth told and Sons CVS on Comedy Central have the same parent company is not stealing
49岁是签订了为期5年的合同价值，并告诉儿子CVS喜剧中央有同一母公司不算偷
much is it is a permanent loan sometimes there right sometimes not so much but for what it's worth this year's long term hurricane forecast is out
钱这是一个永久的贷款有时右有时不那么多，但对于什么是值得今年的长期飓风预测出
the forecaster is at Colorado State Project a quiet Atlantic hurricane season mostly because they say ill Nino will raise the war in the Pacific well the Atlantic waters have been cooling on a trend
预报员是在科罗拉多州项目一个安静的大西洋飓风季节主要是因为他们说生病尼诺将提高在太平洋战争以及大西洋水域已冷却的趋势
we will see you in September muscle car fans look away here are the pictures of the last of the Corvettes that fell into that money to open up the Corvette Museum
我们会看到你在九月肌肉车迷目光移开这里是最后的巡洋舰是掉进钱的开拓克尔维特博物馆的图片
this mangled records used to be a beautiful rocket sled a 2001 z06 all 8 cars are out now some better than others. This one sadly a total loss
曾经是一个美丽的火箭橇2001年的Z06所有的8辆都出来了现在一些比别人做得更好这种错位的记录。这个可悲的是总损失
another big fire in Boston last night when to add alarm sound when they rolled up on a Boston firefighters knew they need a lot of water
再大的火在波士顿的时候添加的报警声，当他们卷起在波士顿消防员昨晚知道他们需要大量的水
and then this is why you don't park in front of a hydrant that's a 4 inch hose running through the windows of somebody's BMW not uncommon one firefighters are in a hurry and someone has been inconsiderate
然后这就是为什么你没有在一个消防栓，这是一个4英寸的软管，通过别人的宝马并不少见1消防队员的Windows上运行的前方停在赶时间，有人一直不体贴
the driver was find $100 bill need to know when does the car was driven away this morning as one firefighter said it's like parking in a handicap spot you just don't do that
司机被发现100美元的钞票需要知道什么时候车子今早赶走为一体的消防队员说，这就像在停车场差点当场你只是不这样做
and the tweet of the day the comeback of the day goes to Julia louis-dreyfus last night we show you her spectacular Rolling Stone cover where in the Constitution are back the way other people wear their hearts on their sleeves and we put it out the problem at John Hancock he signed the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution
而当天的鸣叫一天复出进入朱莉娅路易斯德雷福斯昨晚我们将向您展示她的壮观滚石涵盖宪法是背面的方式与其他人穿他们的心在他们的袖子，我们把它出了问题在约翰·汉考克，他签署了独立宣言和宪法
Dreyfus has cleared it all up and we stand corrected she said the day quotes John Hancock not part of tattoo with a birthmark 1962 photo is proof and sure enough you'll forgive the nudity but there it is in the flesh
德雷福斯已经清除了这一切，我们站在纠正她说，当天援引约翰·汉考克的纹身有胎记1962照片的一部分就是明证果然你能原谅裸体但它是在肉体
when we come back tonight the remarkable come back of a young man living up to the idea of Boston strong
我们回来的时候，今晚的显着回来的年轻人辜负波士顿的想法强
find me tonight in the year since the Boston Marathon bombing we've got to know Jeff Bauman and while he has since gently corrected us that his family name is actually pronounce Bowman the Jeff we came to know either way back then has changed a lot
发现我在今晚，因为我们已经认识了杰夫·鲍曼的波士顿马拉松赛轰炸的一年，而他此后轻轻地纠正我们，他的姓其实是发音鲍曼的杰夫，我们才知道不管怎样那时有了很大的变化
remember we gotta know im from that picture that still hard to look at the blood in the life or draining from his body
记得我们得从那张照片仍然很难看血液在生活中还是从他的身体排水知道IM
while he lost both legs Jeff Bauman survive a day with help is written about his life and struggles and victories in a new book called stronger and recently we went back to Boston to check back in on M st anniversary approaches
虽然他失去了一天了双腿杰夫·鲍曼生存与帮助是写​​了关于他的生活和斗争和胜利的一本新书叫更强，最近我们又回到了波士顿回来检查在M上ST周年来临之际
Jeff Bauman knows the exact moment when his life changed I remember
杰夫·鲍曼知道我还记得他的生活改变的确切时刻
this kid standing next to me to send out a place and he was the setting of the best back in and it was really odd foot look out of my eyes tear down an anaconda
这小子站在我旁边发出一个地方，他是在最好的背部设置，这是非常奇怪的脚看出来我的眼睛推倒水蟒
what in the next instant Tamerlan tsarnaev was gone then Jeffrey members of flash in a pot
怎样在未来的即时塔放tsarnaev不见了然后杰弗里闪光灯成员在一个锅里
what you remember after that called salata Kaos murah be really hot smell really bad
之后那个叫萨拉塔卡奥斯murah你还记得什么是真正热的味道真的很糟糕
smoking everywhere people going crazy does debris all over us and in the chaos with
吸烟的人到处都是快要疯了呢碎片遍布我们，在混乱中与
Bowman bleeding badly there was the man in the cowboy hat to save his life
鲍曼流了很多血有该名男子在牛仔帽，以挽救他的生命
that's a lot of courage to run into something like that not knowing if there could be another bomb what if there was another one
这是一个很大的勇气，遇到这样的事情，不知道是否有可能是另一枚炸弹，如果有另外一个
what if its in Goa
什么，如果它在果阿
does it feel like it's been
它觉得它已经
feels like a month gone by since its everything pencil Quicken
感觉就像一个月过去了，因为它的一切铅笔加快
I've been doing so much Dakota Fighting Sioux
我已经做了这么多达科他州苏族战斗
finding yourself to move forward
发现自己向前走
the pain was unimaginable the physical therapy has been growling but he quickly became part of that Boston strong rallying cry and in the years since Carlos Arredondo the man in the cowboy hat has been at his side so have many of his sports heroes
痛苦是难以想象的物理疗法已被咕咕叫，但他很快就成为了波士顿强振臂高呼的一部分，并在未来数年，因为卡洛斯·阿雷东多的男子在牛仔帽一直在他身边这么有许多他的体育英雄
the Bruins the Socs the Celtics everyone dear to you in Boston sports
熊的SOCS凯尔特人大家亲爱的你在波士顿体育
yeah I can ask for much more
是的，我可以要求更
greatest fight go to a ball game econoprint you back to feel before the tragedy connotation Monterey from everything
最伟大的战斗去看球赛econoprint你回来的悲剧内涵从蒙特利之前的一切感到
his family and friends kept up the study encouragement and his girlfriend Erin who was running in the race that day never left side with in 4 months of losing both legs Jeff Bauman took his first steps just watch you getting around today you get a new set of kicks your doing
他的家人和朋友保持了学习的鼓励和女友艾琳是谁在比赛的那一天永远不会运行左侧有4个月失去了双腿杰夫·鲍曼把他的第一个步骤，只是看你今天让周围你会得到一组新的踢你做
yeah you're doing it that's a big deal if its hard its alright its hard work but it's worth it
是的，你正在做的，这是一个大问题，如果它很难这样很好的辛勤工作，但它是值得的
what's a big nose going to be a dad and husband so that's got that going for you
什么是大鼻子将是一个父亲和丈夫，这样的得到了去为你
does a very nervous but I know it's gonna be great and everyone I talk to says she don't want you hold your child
确实很紧张，但我知道这会是伟大的，每个人都我跟她说，不希望你把你的孩子
the whole different life
全不同的生活
excited to get that new aspect of life how does going to die and now I'm walking around
兴奋地得到新的生命怎么会死的方面，现在我走动
1000 is trucking through a tragic event in coming out can a way better than before
1000是通过一个悲剧性的事件货运在未来能出的方式比以前更好
how about that Jeff Bauman one year later that conversation and many others along with new revelations from the investigation all part of an hour long special report wear a ring tomorrow night on this very station attracts 108 hours from the start of the marathon to capture that second suspect that is tomorrow night at 8
怎么样，杰夫·鲍曼一年后的谈话和其他许多人一起从调查的新启示一小时的所有部分长期特别报道戴戒指明天晚上这个车站就吸引了108小时从马拉松开始捕捉到第二怀疑是明天晚上8时
7 central for now for us that's our broadcast on a Thursday night thank you for being here with us on Brian Williams we hope to see right back here tomorrow evening as we go off the air let's finish
7中央现在对我们来说这是我们的广播上周四晚上谢谢你能在这里和我们的布赖恩·威廉斯，我们希望看到的右后卫在这里明天晚上，我们去停播让我们完成
something beautiful cherry blossoms in Washington judge to be at their peak right
一些美丽的樱花在华盛顿法官是在其高峰期的权利